Om Namah Shivay friends, today let's
talk about the AISI Eye Protection No Problem
Term Insurance. For this,
I want to tell you one thing. AISI Eye
Protection Plan is a very old plan
and they have just added new benefits to this plan.
If you want to know
about
some other features of the product, smart policy, you can quickly go to my old
video.
I have already made an old video for that. I am
providing you the link in the description box. You can go and learn about the complete product,
ideal pitch about the product,
but in today's video,
we are only going to look at the benefit options
in AISI term insurance plan.
Basically, AISI Eye
Protection No Problem Term Insurance, as
you can understand from the name, so whatever you do on the
insurance plan of the revised
premium, you get this plan.
After the policy becomes term insurance, it becomes Steve Jobs.
Then you are given a refund. So let's
talk about that. Okay,
Jaipur. You have to install it.
David No Problem If you want to take a loan, then
basically there are four options from three options
given in it. After clicking on any one of these four options, you can select
any one option.
Now we can stop on it. The
first option is of return of premium, you
can select cough syrup. In
whichever option you get, you get income benefit offer
and the third option you get is
Return No Problem with Live Stage Power
and the fourth option which you get is Early
Return of Premium with Live Stage Cover.
You can enroll in regular Priyanka policy by using any one of these four options.
So first of all, if you want to know
about return of premium, then let me
try to explain a little bit to you
that in Reena experiment, what you are going to get for life, if you take
basic time Chudawat, then it is
basically limited, like it will be
₹5000000 or whatever
option combination you want to take, that does
not change from time to time. In this policy, it
means that it is only about this much premium for you.
Also, when you select the next option of
protection, suppose
you have taken a policy of ₹1 and have selected the
first option of With the Return of PM. If nothing happens to
you in the policy direction,
when the policy goes to the last place,
then you get 105 percent of your premium paid back.
Okay, you get a refund of
105 percent, which I am refunding you.
For this, you are
deducting the premium from time to time.
If you have taken some iron benefit in your policy,
like accident cover, what do you do,
you
can take the same thing, difficult benefit, medical benefits.
That is also an option thing, you do not get the money for that thing,
you are
paying only the money for basic protection.
And one more thing, if for some
reason you stop doing it on the screen
and your policy lapses, then
you have to renew the policy by paying some late payment charge. At
that time, you have to  If
I remove the job alert by paying the loading charge, then
that renewal is
not referred to you,
subscribe through which they call you,
okay, so the other benefit options that
I have already
subscribed to you and
subscribed, but in this
you choose the incumbency factor office, in this
you have to choose initially at the time, okay,
it is also the same, but the money that you will get
when the policy becomes expensive, okay, you will
not get it at that time, in this policy which is running, whatever
income you earn
on your interest, it is refunded to you,
like and so it is the same, okay, so now
see in this, then when you do this side, then in this you get the
benefit, in this you are given point to
point
subscription, it is given to
you in the minister and till the completion of the
policy,
you are given a pure on a regular monthly basis,
you get 1% or 2%
in such a situation, only then you get an obscure, that is
how much you
want, that you give points  You have taken it above, okay,
and you will be able to
subscribe till you turn 2 years old,
okay, so you
subscribe, then
subscribe to the score, so in explaining this thing,
I will tell you about you,
I will tell you, right now see, if you have taken the policy, you have
chosen a cover period of ₹ 2500000,
okay, and you have made the payment of the policy for 10
years, okay, and what is there in it, you have
explained it to you,
you buy the policy from them,
whatever your life process is, when
you turn 20 years old, okay, at that time
after getting educated, the next policy will
come, then you should
subscribe, like let me tell you that if
you have taken the benefit option in this,
subscribe,
subscribe, subscribe to
this channel,
after sending it, you are getting the money back
and when you die in this seven
policy, that is, when you turn 70 years old, you
die with the job, at that time
you will get 10 years of it, so from here you will get it in 10 years,
but subscribe to Amazing thousand 210,
milk, curd,
ghee, it gets
exhausted on subscription, therefore
Subscribe but it happens here
so subscribed and
subscribed to that
ok now we talk about change in rate job
stage cover in this you will get policy in APN, then it will become
smaller then you are
given pure but when you have booked your life there are
some changes on it like
you have booked life here ok
suppose for one crore rupees ok you
get ₹50 for yourself choose this
subscribe here
I will talk about rate use with
life discovery this is the third
benefit option right in this when you are
buying the policy then
now we will talk about return of
premium with a life this is the
second benefit option,
after buying your life your life cover in the policy i.e. the
time remaining gets changed
but you get your money when the policies get
updated 2015 match today then only
on unmarried you get
105 likes by drinking total love as much as you want
but now you are making changes in likes and in this it
means this  It happens automatically, like if
you are a first order senior officer, the semester will
remain the same as you are planning,
suppose you have saved a time limit of Rs 50 lakh here,
then
your remaining time in the first policy will be
Rs 5000000, is this okay? And from your
control senior till the completion of this chapter,
your time will keep increasing every year,
suppose in your second
policy year, you have Rs 50 lakh in your first policy
and in the second policy
senior, your time will increase by five percent,
see, Rs 5000000 from this policy, its 250000 is
not used, you will have to
control it, in the third policy,
subscribe to the policy when you are in
school or whatever you
subscribe to, it does
not get subscribed
and you
subscribe to Rs 6, in
such a situation, the remaining Rs 5 from the office will remain the same,
okay, and from this year
till the end of the policy, your
life is tied to taking time, that is a
question, that means here the time of Rs 1 is
in this  Let me tell you, see
if you have subscribed for
34th time
and share
and
subscription is happening, it gets
subscribed,
okay, this
subscription is getting
subscribed,
okay, it remains fixed, it
stops incrementing after that, after reaching
crores have courage
06, okay, it will get subscribed after taking the fees,
as you can see,
okay, after that now subscribe from school till the end
and if it happens here, you get it,
if you get it here, then
your family can get so much money, if you get
subscribed,
now send it to school,
today also whatever you have decided, whatever
love you have shown,
you will be honored with it,
so let us now talk in general in the next report
with a live stage cover, this is the fourth option,
in the fourth option, some understanding has been
set in this, in this you are
getting money after this and in the third option, when you get
processed, you are getting money
and in the fourth option,
you will get money while the policy is running.  I am getting it,
yes, okay, like, and I am the richest,
I made you feel relaxed,
in the first policy care, except for your time, the
option here is as much as you have used,
till the control is on the feet of the CSK written Yagya, your incremental 5s, your time gets
increased and your time till this holiday
hole Rafaeli cases, your time
which you have got the opportunity gets converted back
and you will get 50% of what you have given
in the old fashion in the Interpol system from one year,
okay, and
when will you get the pure in which the policy will be effective,
then you will not get the pure, but
you have to decide
when you want the job vote, if you are doing the policy of control,
in the fourth option, if you are enrolling, then only
you have to tell
when you want the money, you want it when you will become six years old
or you want it when you will become 70 years old, then
you will get this and respect, if you
want it by taking it in exchange, then
you will be given the same amount,
dinner five per cent of total prepaid or
a page  When symptoms appear, it will be given to you,
you have to choose it initially,
okay, whatever movie I refund you in this,
I confirm it once inside you
that whatever you are watching
on your screen, then one and a half inch
question arose that it does not happen in the past because
in this, if you
put its benefit for medical benefit in the benefit, okay,
I am telling you this again, then it is
not repaired, only the best
premium is refunded to you,
okay, in this plan,
if you want to choose more benefits from it, as
you can see in this policy,
more benefits are given to you, like if
you take this plan, then death benefit, pure
life, enjoy life, lessons of life and
helpless option, an all in one option, left
benefit, in this, if you take live classes, then you get
my life and plus accident tax,
okay, a life only and only yes,
okay, you have to select these options also,
coming to this fort, I have  I have
already made a separate video for you,
I have already given its link in the description box, you
can watch its complete video which is also Aadhar free, through which you
can see here how much is the premium payment, how much
calculation has to be done,
what is De Villiers, what is the death benefit, I have already made a
spring for this because he tweeted
a new president at 9 PM, the same
oil polish happened in two wars, I want to do more, that's all
for today, thank you.